♪ AH UH AH UH ♪
♪ YEAH RIHANNA ♪
♪ GOOD GIRL GONE BAD ♪
♪ AH UH AH UH ♪
♪ TAKE THREE ♪
♪ ACTION ♪
♪ NO CLOUDS IN MY STORMS ♪
♪ LET IT RAIN
I HYDROPLANE INTO FAME ♪
♪ COME ON DOWN WITH
THE DOW JONES ♪
♪ WHEN THE CLOUDS COME WE GONE ♪
♪ WE ROCHELLA ♪
♪ SHE FLY HIGHER THAN WEATHER ♪
♪ AND SHE ROCKS IT BETTER ♪
♪ YOU KNOW ME ♪
♪ AN ANTICIPATION
FOR PRECIPITATION ♪
♪ STACKS CHIPS FOR
THE RAINY DAY ♪
♪ JAY RAIN MAN IS BACK
WITH LIL MS. SUNSHINE ♪
♪ RIHANNA WHERE YOU AT ♪
♪ YOU HAD MY HEART ♪
♪ AND WE'LL NEVER
BE WORLD APART ♪
♪ MAYBE IN MAGAZINES ♪
♪ BUT YOU'LL STILL BE MY STAR ♪
♪ BABY CAUSE IN THE DARK ♪
♪ YOU CAN SEE SHINY CARS ♪
♪ AND THAT'S WHEN
YOU NEED ME THERE ♪
♪ WITH YOU I'LL ALWAYS SHARE ♪
♪ BECAUSE ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN SHINES ♪
♪ WE'LL SHINE TOGETHER ♪
♪ TOLD YOU I'LL
BE HERE FOREVER ♪
♪ SAID I'LL ALWAYS
BE YOUR FRIEND ♪
♪ TOOK AN OATH ♪
♪ I'M A STICK IT
OUT 'TILL THE END ♪
♪ NOW THAT IT'S RAINING
MORE THAN EVER ♪
♪ KNOW THAT WE STILL
HAVE EACH OTHER ♪
♪ YOU CAN STAND
UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ ELLA EL LA EH EH EH ♪
♪ UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH EH EH ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH
EH EH EH EH EH ♪
♪ THESE FANCY THINGS ♪
♪ WILL NEVER COME IN BETWEEN ♪
♪ YOU'RE PART OF MY ENTITY ♪
♪ HERE FOR INFINITY ♪
♪ WHEN THE WAR HAS
TOOK IT'S PART ♪
♪ WHEN THE WORLD HAS
DEALT IT'S CARDS ♪
♪ IF THE HAND IS HARD ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL
MEND YOUR HEART ♪
♪ BECAUSE ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN SHINES ♪
♪ WE'LL SHINE TOGETHER ♪
♪ TOLD YOU I'LL
BE HERE FOREVER ♪
♪ SAID I'LL ALWAYS
BE YOUR FRIEND ♪
♪ TOOK AN OATH ♪
♪ I'M A STICK IT
OUT 'TILL THE END ♪
♪ NOW THAT IT'S RAINING
MORE THAN EVER ♪
♪ KNOW THAT WE STILL
HAVE EACH OTHER ♪
♪ YOU CAN STAND
UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH EH EH ♪
♪ UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH
EH EH EH EH EH ♪
♪ YOU CAN RUN INTO MY ARMS ♪
♪ IT'S OKAY DON'T BE ALARMED ♪
♪ COME INTO ME ♪
♪ THERE'S NO DISTANCE
IN BETWEEN OUR LOVE ♪
♪ SO GONNA LET THE RAIN POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE ALL YOU
NEED AND MORE ♪
♪ BECAUSE ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN SHINES ♪
♪ WE'LL SHINE TOGETHER ♪
♪ TOLD YOU I'LL
BE HERE FOREVER ♪
♪ SAID I'LL ALWAYS
BE YOUR FRIEND ♪
♪ TOOK AN OATH ♪
♪ I'M A STICK IT
OUT 'TILL THE END ♪
♪ NOW THAT IT'S RAINING
MORE THAN EVER ♪
♪ KNOW THAT WE STILL
HAVE EACH OTHER ♪
♪ YOU CAN STAND
UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH EH EH ♪
♪ UNDER MY UMBRELLA ♪
♪ EL LA EL LA EH
EH EH EH EH EH ♪
♪ IT'S RAINING RAINING ♪
♪ OH BABY IT'S RAINING ♪
♪ BABY COME INTO ME ♪
♪ COME INTO ME ♪
♪ IT'S RAINING RAINING ♪
♪ OH BABY IT'S RAINING ♪
♪ YOU CAN ALWAYS COME INTO ME ♪